Guide to the Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Collection 1938-[1970-1998] 2000
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Series VI: Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Central Records Library
  - Sub-series 1: Central Records Library
    - CRL 13020 Letter to Claimants Notifying of Raise in ADR Cap to $20000, Mailed with ADR Election Form, Rules and Q and A 1993, 1995 (Box 59)
    - CRL 13021 Attorney Rejection Letter/SC Clarification Letter 1993 (Box 59)
    - CRL 13022 Mass Mailing Report [1986-1992] (Box 59)
    - CRL 13023 Letter Offering ADR to LIT/ARB Claimants 1993 (Box 59)
    - CRL 13024-13025 Pro Rata Payment Letter for Claimants in SC Process; Press Release 1995 (Box 59)
    - CRL 13026 Prospective Claimant Letter; Order Re: LDS Claimants [1990] (Box 59)
    - CRL 13027 Information on Appeal from Conflicting User Claim n.d. (Box 59)
    - CRL 13028 Instructions to Breland Claimants to File a DSCT Late Claim [1991] (Box 59)
    - CRL 13029 Order to Accept Late Claims with Letter of Explanation 1990 (Box 59)
    - CRL 13030 Order Regarding Payment of Pro Rata Distribution Funds [and Mailing List] 1995, 4 folders (Box 59)
    - CRL 13031 Option One Warning Mailing (Category 1-1A Mailing) 1994 (Box 60)
    - CRl 13032 Stalled Claims in SC Mailing (Category 6 Mailing) Mailed on 4/15/94-Warned of 7/15/94 Deadline 1994 (Box 60)
    - CRL 13033 LAMS [Litigation and Arbitration Management System] No Elect Mailing (Category 5) 1994 (Box 60)
    - CRL 13034 Option Packets Mailed to Outstanding Option 2/3 Claims (Category 1 User/Nonuser); Mailing List 1994 (Box 60)
    - CRL 13035 Mailing of Options Packets to Option 2 Rejections No Elects (Category 4 Mailing); Mailed April 1, 1995 1995 (Box 60)
    - CRL 13036 Mailing to Option 1/5 Elects with No Election Form in House (Category 1A) 1994 (Box 60)
    - CRL 13036A Packets Sent to Option 2/3 Claimants with No Queue Number, Cover Letter Warning of 8/1/94 Deadling; Mailing List 1994, 7 folders (Box 60-61)
    - CRL 13037 Option 4 Follow Up Packet Warning of 4/30/93 Deadline to Elect, Mailed 29-Jan-93 1993 (Box 61)
    - CRL 13038 Last Chance Packet. Deadline of Option Election of 7/1/91 Warning, Mailed on 01-May-91 1991 (Box 61)
    - CRL 13040 Press Release Process for Late Claim Deadline 1994, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - CRl 13041 Pro Rata Stuffer (Insert for Pro Rata Checks) 1996 (Box 61)
    - CRL 13042-13044 Packet Mailed to Option 2 Rejections that have not Elected Option 3 or Accepted their Offer, Cover Letter Dated 9/18/95 1995 (Box 61)
    - CRL 13045 Notice of OTR Bar Date of 4/1/96 [Dalkon ACP Mailing List] 1996 (Box 144 Oversize)
    - CRL 13046 Order Regarding Pro Rata Payments After 31-Dec-95--Mailed on 2/13/96 to Attorneys 1995-1996 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13047 Complaint Certification Deadline Warning of 01-Apr-96 Deadline -Mailed 16-Feb-96-to Legal Claimants who Have Not Decided 1996 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13048 Packet Warning of Disallowance 4/1/96 1996 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13049-13051 Packets Mailed to Offers Outstanding >725, Warning of the 5/1/96 Deadline 1996 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13052-13053 Option 4 and D Activation Mailing 1994-1995 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13054 Letter Reminding Claimants of Final 5/1/96 Deadline 1996 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13055 LDS Warning Postcard of 6-30-95 Deadline, Mailed 6/1/95 1995 (Box 62)
    - CRL 13056 Mailing Re: The Opportunity to Accept Offer-ADR Elects Received Mailing (Mailed 5/1/96) 1995-1996 (Box 62-63)
    - CRL 13057 Warning Letter of 2/1/95 Deadline for SC Claimants who have not Returned a SC Questionnaire or Medical Authorization-Mailed on 10/26/94 1994-1995 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13058 Proof of Postage and Invoices for Newsletters-Used by Legal in Most Instances to Support Mailings 1994-1996 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13059 LDS Phillipine Claim Disallowance Mailing 1994 (Box 63)
      Mailing list in Oversize Box 144, removed by DSCT Redaction Team, 2/2004
    - CRL 13060 Claim Type ID Mailing, Included Option 1/5 Options 1990 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13061-13063 Breland Claim Mailings; Letter to Inform Breland Claimants of an Additional 30% Payment 1993-1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13064 Disallowance of Fraudulent Claims Report 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13065 Mailing to Option C Claimbooks with No Signature 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13066 Request for Option 3 Claimants with no Signed Claimbook to Return Claim Book by 11/2/94 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13067 Notification of Change of Address for Special Program PO Box 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13068 Notification of Discontinuance of ART [Administrative Review Team] Process 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13069 Offer of Option One to Non-Users that Were Offered Less than Option One Amount 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13070 Notification to Breland Claims of the Discontinuance of BART 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13071 Notification of 3/1/95 Deadline to Submit ADR [Alternative Dispute Resolution] Agreement 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13072 Notification to LIT/ARB Claimants of the Availability of Re-review 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13073 Notification of Deficient LDS Claim and Warning of 8/31/94 Deadline to Submit Materials 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13073A Complete Listing of Disallowed Claims for Failure to Submit a Completed Claim Package 1994 (Box 63)
    - CRL 13074 Notification of Late Claim Request Received after Deadline 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13075 Option 3 No Elect Mailing, Requesting Election by 12/1/94 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13076 Claimant Newsletter Mailing to Attorneys That Were Not Forwarding Them to Claimants 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13077 Notification of the Removal of the Review Hold Placed on IVF [In Vitro Fertilization] Claims Effective 1/1/95 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13078 Notification of Deadline to Proceed with the Option 2/3 Claims Stalled, (60 Days) 1995 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13079 Notification to Stalled Option 2/3 Claims Requesting Action by 6/1/94 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13080 Notification of 6/1/94 Deadline to Proceed with Option 2/3 Joint Claims Stalled in Process 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13081 Special Option One Mailing to Claimants Not Previously Elegible 1993-1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13082 Notification to Late Claims of the Hold on Reclassification Process 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13083 LDS Address Update Mailing 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13084 Follow Up to Special Option One Mailing 1994 (Box 64)
    - CRL 13085 Mailing of ADR Claimants Ability to Accept their Settlement Offer 1996 (Box 65)
    - CRL 13086 Mailing of Warning of 10/1/96 Deadline to Choose ADR/LIT/ARB Offer 1996, 5 folders (Box 65)
      Mailing list in folder no. 1 removed by DSCT Redaction Team, 2/2004
    - CRL 13078A-13078D Second Warning of 10/1/96 Deadline, Sent Certified 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13088 Letter Sent with Corrected Breland Release, Mailed 8/2/96 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13089 Letter from PAC [Private Adjudication Center] Explaining Revisions to the Scheduling Process, Trust Assuming Scheduling Responsibilities 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13090 Elimination of ADR Mailing, for Breland Claims 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13090B Notice of Elimination of ADR from DSCT Trustee 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13091 Postcard of Third Warning of 10/1/96 Deadline 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13092 Mailing to ADR Attorneys with more than 5 Claims in ADR 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13093 ADR Notification Letter Mailing 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13094 Compliance Audit of 60% Pro Rata 1996 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13095 Outstanding Pro Rata Check Warning Letter 1997 (Box 66)
    - CRL 13096-13096A Lutz Mailing; Lutz Mailing Resulting from Appeals Court Ruling 1997 (Box 67)
    - CRL 13097 LIT/ARB Mailing Offering ADR Election Until 7/31/97 1997 (Box 67)
    - CRL 13098 PAC Address Update Mailing 1997 (Box 67)
    - CRL 13099 Collection of Press Releases 1988-1996 (Box 67)
    - CRL 13100 Pro Rata III Notification Letter/Deadline to Cash n.d., 4 folders (Box 67)
      Documents with claimant identification removed by DSCT Redaction Team, 2/2004
    - CRL 13101 Pro Rata III Warning Letter (3/1/99) Deadline 1999 (Box 68)
    - CRL 14002, 14004-14032 Miscellaneous Letters Sent By DSCT Regarding Medical Records and Information [1990-1992] (Box 68)
    - CRL 14003 Late Claimant not Eligible for Special Program [1990-1992] (Box 68)
    - CRL 14033 Report of Cases in the Special Program (InVitro Fertilization Program) 1990-1992 (Box 68)
      Documents with claimant information removed by DSCT Redaction Team, 2/2004
    - CRL 14034 Program Development Work Papers for the Special Program 1988-1989 (Box 68)
    - CRL 14035 [Special Program Correspondence with Doctors.] Resumes 1990-1995, 3 folders (Box 69)
    - CRL 14036, 14038-14047 Special Program/IVF Packet n.d. (Box 69)
    - CRL 14037 Special Program Information Request 1988 (Box 69)
    - CRL 14048 Listing of the Trust's Consulting Physicians 1994 (Box 69)
    - CRL 14049 List of [IVF] Offer Calculations with Dividend n.d. (Box 69)
    - CRL 15001-15003 Trust Initial Offer Letters for Conflict Claim, to IVF Program Participants and for Compensable Claimants 1993, 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15000, 15004 Breland Initial Offer Letters for Conflict Claim and Compensable Claimant 1993 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15006-15007 In-Depth Review Offer Letters 1993 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15008 Breland Final Offer Letter 1993 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15009 Trust Final Offer Letters 1991-1994 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15010 Joint Offer Letters and Procedures 1993 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15011 LAMS Re-Review Offer Letters 1995 (Box 69)
    - CRL 15012-15019 [DSCT Re-Review Offer Letters] 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16000 Option 2 General Release of Claims 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16001 Option 3 General Release of Claims 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16002 General Release of Claims-Survivor Release n.d. (Box 69)
    - CRL 16003 Breland General Release of Claims 1995-1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16004 Release B for OTR Corporate Claimants 1990 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16006 Release with Future Pro Rata Payment 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16007 Release with Dividend 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16009, 16011 Agreements to Limit Attorneys Fees and Costs [sample] 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 16010 General Release of Claims-Survival Release 1996 (Box 69)
    - CRL 17000 45 Day Packet Explanation Letter 1993 (Box 69)
    - CRL 17004 45 Day Packet (LIT/ARB Information) 1991-1995 (Box 69)
    - CRL 17005 91st Day Packet n.d. (Box 69)
    - CRL 17006 91st Day Packet Letter 1993 (Box 69)
    - DSCT Claim Review Form 1990-1994 (Box 69a)
    - DSCT General Release of Claims Forms n.d. (Box 69a)
    - DSCT Miscellaneous Forms 1988 (Box 69a)
    - Forms: Child Claim Form 1993-1994 (Box 69a)
    - Forms: Husband Claim Forms 1990 (Box 69a)
    - Forms: User Claim Valuation Worksheet 1990-1991 (Box 69a)
    - CRL 17007 45 Day Packet Letter 1994-1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 17008 Rejection Packet 1993 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18000-18020 [Settlement Conference Letters Master Copy Notebook] 1991-1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18100 Additional Information Sheet With and Without Deadline Warning Section 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18104 SC Confidentiality Agreement 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18106 [SC] Acceptance Considerations 1995-1996 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18110 Settlement Conference Packet Label 3 for Special Releases 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18111 Settlement Conference Packet Label 1 for Offers Greater than $725 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18112 Settlement Conference Packet Label 2 for Offers Less than $725 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18113 Settlement Conference Packet Label 4 for Offers Greater Than $300 and Less Than $725 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18114 Pro Rata Distribution Chart 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18201 Breland SC Materials Packet with Offers Greater Than $725 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18202 Breland SC Materials Packet for Claims Less than $725 1995 (Box 70)
    - CRL 18203 Breland SC Materials Packets (Special Release) 1995 (Box 71)
    - CRL 18204 Acceptance Considerations for BIT Claims 1995-1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19000 Rules Governing ADR [Alternative Dispute Resolution] 1992-1994, 1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19001 Common Questions about ADR, Q& A 1993-1995 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19002 ADR Results 1993-1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19003 ADR Considerations 1995-1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19004 ADR Election Packet Cover Letter 1992-1994 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19005 ADR Election Packet 1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19006 ADR Introduction Letters 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19007 ADR vs. In-Depth Settlement Conference Information Packet 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19008 ADR Glossary 1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19009 In-Depth SC/ADR Election Form 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19010 ADR Agreement 1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19011 PAC [Private Adjudication Center, Inc.] Introduction Letter 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19012 DSCT Claims Resolutions Election Form for ADR Only (Single and Joint Forms) 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19013 ADR Agreement Cover Letter 1992-1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19015 ADR Survey 1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19016 ADR Internal Forms/Correspondence 1992 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19017 Breland ADR/ARB Election Form 1995 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19108 Breland Package for Option C Rejections No Elects 1995 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19019-19021 Breland SC Rejection Packet Cover Letter Detailing ADR and Arbitration Choices 1995-1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19022 BIT Claims Resolution Election Form for ADR Only (Joint and Single Forms) 1995-1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19023 Guidelines for Security of ADR Advocates at Hearings 1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19024 Pre-Hearing Call Informational Sheet for Referees with Cover Letter 1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19025-19028 Joint Resolution and Election Form; Guidelines for Prehearing Calls; Prehearing Call Observation Sheet; Rejection and Election Form 1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19029-19031 ADR Checklist and Forms 1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19032 ADR Notification Letters 1996 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19033 ADR Task Force-ADR Cap Changes to $20000, Fast Track Arbitration Eliminated 1993-1994 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19034 ADR Summary of Proposal to Increase Award to $20000 1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19035 Letter Mailed to Claimants Informing them of the Increase in the ADR Cap to $20,000 1993 (Box 71)
    - CRL 19036 Mailing to ADR-Accept Offer with 75% Dividend 1996 (Box 72)
    - CRL 19037 Private Adjudication Center Program Summary n.d., 2 folders (Box 72)
    - CRL 19038 Original Case Specific Affadavits [CSA's] DS Number Order, Vols. 1-7 1995-1996, 31 folders (Box 72-77)
    - CRL 19039 General Affadavits Exchanged/CVS for Doctors 1995-1997 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20000 Rules Governing Regular Arbitration 1991, 1995, 1997 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20001-20002 Common Questions About Binding Arbitration; Arbitration Glossary 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20003 Jury Trial and Arbitration Results 1994, 1996 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20004 Rules Governing Fast-Track Arbitration n.d. (Box 78)
    - CRL 20005-20007 Trial and Arbitration Considerations; Election Form for Litigation/Arbitration 1995-1996 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20008 Defining an Arbitration Policy 1991 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20009 New Arbitration Rules Mailing 1995 (Box 78)
    - CRL 20010-20011 Arbitration Election Forms for DSCT and Breland 1996-1997 (Box 78)
    - CRL 21000 Rossman Information 1991-1992 (Box 78)
    - CRL 21004 DSCT History and Background Sent to Local Counsel for Orientation Purposes 1991, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - CRL 21005 Common Questions About Trial 1996 (Box 78)
    - CRl 21006 Sample 120 Day Deadline Warning to Commence or Recommence Litigation Against Trust Per Order 1996 (Box 78)
    - CRL 21007 Trial Election Form for DSCT 1996 (Box 78)
    - CRL 21008 Philippine Pleadings 1994-1996 (Box 78)
    - CRL 21009A Order and Report of Disallowance of Philippine Late Claims 1994-1995 (Box 79)
    - CRL 21012 Litigation Factors 1991 (Box 79)
    - CRL 21013 Policy Manual for Litigation/Arbitration 1992, 3 folders (Box 79)
    - CRL 21014 Information Packets Provided to Local Counsel 1992-1993, 5 folders (Box 79-80)
    - CRL 21015 Legal Resource Team Procedures 1993, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - CRL 22000 Daily Option Count Forms 1990-1991, 3 folders (Box 80)
    - CRL 22001-22003 Non DS Users and Related Derivative Claims Listing; Type Conflict Report; Domestic and Foreign Claimants w/Pre 1968 Insertions and Domestic Claimants w/Post 1976 Insertions; Derivative Future Claims Report 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 81)
    - CRL 22004 Reclassification Request Forms 1989, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - CRL 22005 Option 3 Weekly Status Reports 1990-1991, 6 folders (Box 82-83)
    - CRL 22006 Option 2 Weekly Status Reports 20-Apr-90 Through 4-Oct-91, and 1/9/95 Through 7/28/95 [Breland] 1990-1991, 1995, 3 folders (Box 83)
    - CRL 22007 Listing of Claimants who were Compensated for their Injuries Prior to the Robins Bankruptcy 1991 (Box 83)
    - CRL 22008 Priority Change Status Reports and Documentation [Memoranda] 1990-1992 (Box 83)
    - CRL 22010 Quarterly Option 3 Productivity Study 1991-1992 (Box 83)
    - CRL 22011 Quarterly Option 3 Claim Composition Report 1992 (Box 83)
    - CRL 22012 Other Claimants Trust and Breland Insurance Trust Summary July 2, 1991 1991 (Box 83)
    - CRL 22013 Summary of Option 3 Claims and Totals for All DS Claim Options By Attorney [Weekly Report] 1992-1995, 8 folders (Box 84-85)
    - CRL 22014 Option 3 Rejection Report for DS and LDS Claimants 1995 (Box 85)
    - CRL 22015 Claims Dept. Summary Report 7/91 1991 (Box 85)
    - CRL 22016 Summary of Option C Claims and Totals for all Breland Claim Options by Attorney 1995 (Box 85)
    - CRL 22018 List of Claims Disallowed as a Result of the 10/1/96 Deadline 1996 (Box 85)
    - CRL 22019 Results for the 7/1/96 Mailing 1996 (Box 85)
    - CRL 23001 DSCT Management Reports 1990-1996, 60 folders; also Box 145 oversize (Box 85-96)
    - CRL 23002 LDS [Late Dalkon Shield] Management Reports for the Late Claims 1995-1996, 7 folders (Box 96-98)
    - CRL 23003 Breland Insurance Trust Management Report 1991, 1994-1996, 4 folders (Box 98)
    - CRL 23004 ADR [Alternative Dispute Resolution] Weekly Reports 1995 (Box 98)
    - CRL 23039 Option 3 Offers 1993 (Box 98)
    - CRL 24000 Late Claims Training Manual n.d. (Box 99)
    - CRL 24001 LDS Bardate Information/Process 1994, 2 folders (Box 99)
    - CRL 24002 Documentation of the Development of the LDS Claim Packets 1994, 2 folders (Box 99)
    - CRL 24003 List of LDS Numbers Voided and Reassigned 1989 (Box 99)
    - CRL 24004 LDS Court Recommendation Process 1990-1992 (Box 99)
    - CRL 24005-24007 Late Claim Application, Mailing to Late Claim Appellants, LDS Address Update/Notification of Disallowance Letter 1995 (Box 100)
    - CRL 24015 Late Claims Reports 1990-1991, 8 folders (Box 100)
    - [CRL 24015] LDS [Late Dalkon Shield] First Report Objections [1990] (Box 101)
    - [CRL 24015] LDS Objections to DSCT Late Claim Recommendations and Request of Hearing 1990, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - [CRL 24015] LDS Medical Review Chronology First Report 1990, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - CRL 24016 Late Claims Review Process Notebook n.d. (Box 102)
    - CRL 24018 Late Filed Claims Q& A Portion of Script as of 7/5/90 1990 (Box 102)
    - CRL 24200 Late Claim Option Packet 1995 (Box 102)
    - CRL 25001 Memo Re Breland Matter Processing System 1989 (Box 102)
    - CRL 25002 Holdback Explanation for Breland Claimants n.d. (Box 102)
    - CRL 25003 Executive Director's Correspondence Regarding Breland 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 103)
    - CRL 25004 Breland Estimation Project Details 1991, 2 folders (Box 103)
    - CRL 25005 Breland Reimbursement of Search Fee Letters 1992 (Box 103)
    - CRL 25006 Breland Final Warning Postcard of 12/31/95 Deadline 1995 (Box 103)
    - CRL 25007 Breland Tax Forms 1991, 1993 (Box 103)
    - CRL 25008 List of Breland Claimants 1989, 4 folders (Box 103-104)
    - CRL 25009 LDS Log for Claim Number Assignments 1987-1990 (Box 104)
    - CRL 25010 Breland Matter Class B Packets 1988 (Box 104)
    - CRL 25012 Press Release Increase in Breland Holdback February 16, 1994 1994 (Box 104)
    - CRL 25013 Breland Claim Study 1992 (Box 104)
    - CRL 25014 Breland Distribution Planning Folder 1992-1993 (Box 104)
    - CRL 25016 Aetna Binders. Information Provided to and from Aetna for Aetna Project 1991-1996, 10 folders (Box 104-106)
    - CRL 25017 Breland Termination Documents 1998 (Box 106)
    - CRL 26000 OTR [Other Claimants Trust] Certificate of Resolution (Consummation) 1989 (Box 106)
    - CRL 26001-OTR Trustees Minutes 1988-1996, 5 folders (Box 106a)
    - CRL 26002 OTR Taxes 1989-1991 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26003 OTR Claims Resolution Procedure [1988] (Box 107)
    - CRL 26004 Director and Officer's Insurance Liability Policy 1990 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26005 OTR Investment Manager Reports/ Policies and Procedures 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box 107)
    - CRL 26007, 26012 OTR Offer Letter Mailing 1990 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26008 OTR Offer Letter Mailing 1990 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26009 OTR Forms 1990 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26010 OTR Claim Payment Procedures 1990 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26011 OTR Accounting Procedures (w/"OTR Claims 6/95") 1990 (Box 107)
    - CRL 26012 Report of DS Claims Estimation Process for OTR 1988 (Box 108)
    - CRL 26013 Agreement on Transfer of Funds of OTR to DSCT Due to the Termination of the Other Trust 1988 (Box 108)
    - CRL 26014 AH Robins Dear Doctor Letter for Removal Program 1984 (Box 108)
    - CRL (no #) OTR Memorandum of Law 1988-1995, 2 folders (Box 108)
    - CRL (no #) OTR Claims 1995 (Box 108)
    - CRL 27000 Claims Resolution Report. DSCT Newsletters (Numbers 1-14) 1989-1994 (Box 108)
    - CRL 27001 Attorney Update Newsletters 1990-1991 (Box 108)
    - CRL 27002 Late Claims Reporter. Newsletter to LDS Claimants 1990-1994 (Box 108)
    - CRL 27003 The Bulletin. Newsletter to Breland Claimants 1990-1993 (Box 108)
    - CRL 27004 Trust Us. Monthly Newsletter for DSCT Employees 1989-1996, 2 folders (Box 109)
    - CRL 27005 DSCT Counsel Update 1992 (Box 109)
    - CRL 28001 Office Procedures for Temporary Staff Assigned by the Court 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 109)
    - CRL 28003 Breland/LDS Procedures 1990-1991, 3 folders (Box 109-110)
    - CRL 28004 Settlement Conference Procedures 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 110)
    - CRL 28005 Settlement Conference Script (Merged with DSCT and Bit Phone Scripts) 1995-1996 (Box 110)
    - CRL 28006 Script for the Slideshow for New Employees 1995 (Box 110)
    - CRL 28007 Attorney Change Procedures 1993, 1995 (Box 110)
    - CRL 28008 Accounting Procedures 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 110)
    - CRL 28009 Personal Contact Script and Settlement Conference Script for DSCT and BIT Claimants 1990-1996, 5 folders (Box 110-111)
    - CRL 28010 Other Trust Claims Resolution Procedure 1990 (Box 111)
    - CRL 28011-28012 Special Check Procedure; Shredding Procedures 1993 (Box 111)
    - CRL 28013 Safety Policy 1994 (Box 111)
    - CRL 28014 Misfiled Document Procedure 1994 (Box 111)
    - CRL 28015 System Access Procedures 1993 (Box 111)
    - CRL 28016 Document Retention Policy 1992-1994, 2 folders (Box 111-112)
    - CRL 28018 Operations Department Procedures Manuals 1990-1994, 7 and 3 folders (Box 112-113)
    - CRL 28019 Records Management Policy 1992-1993 (Box 113)
    - CRL 28020 Re-Review Policy 1992 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28021 Vital Records Policy 1991 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28022 Merger Procedures From Court 1988 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28023 Special Program Procedures and Memoranda 1989-1991 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28024 Guide to Form Letters System 1989 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28025 Procedures for Option One Audit in 1988 1988 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28026 Policy and Procedures for Claims not Meeting the 7/1/91 Deadline 1991 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28027 Procedures for Transfering Litcon Claims to ADR 1994 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28028 Procedures for Option 2 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - CRL 28029 Communications Department Policies and Procedures Manual 1990, 1992, 1997, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - CRL 28030 Blue/Black Procedures 199 (Box 114)
    - CRL 28031 Late Claims Procedures 1991 (Box 115)